gowallet.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy policy | GoWallet.com

Rev. Sept. 2012

## Facts: What does Blackhawk do with your personal information?

### Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

### What?

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number
  * Account balances
  * Account transactions
  * Transaction history
  * Purchase history

When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

### How?

All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Blackhawk chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

## Reasons we can share your personal information

| Does Blackhawk share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes –** such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes –** to offer our products and services to you | Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other financial institutions** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –** information about your transactions and experiences | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes –** information about your creditworthiness | No | We don't share  
**For our affiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
  
### Questions?

Call 888-633-9432

## Who we are

### Who is providing this notice?

Blackhawk Network, Inc. ("Blackhawk")

## What we do

### How does Blackhawk protect my personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

### How does Blackhawk collect my personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you:

  * open an account
  * give us your contact information
  * show your driver's license
  * show your government-issued ID
  * provide account information

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

### Why can't I limit all sharing?

Federal law gives you the right to limit only:

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.

## Definitions

### Affiliates

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Blackhawk's affiliates include companies with a Blackhawk name and others, such as Safeway Inc. 

### Nonaffiliates

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Blackhawk does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.

### Joint Marketing

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * Blackhawk may partner with nonaffiliated financial companies to jointly market financial products or services to you.

## Other Important Information

CA residents: Blackhawk will limit sharing with our affiliates to the extent required by California law. Blackhawk will not share your personal information for joint marketing with other financial institutions.

VT residents: If Blackhawk shares your personal information for joint marketing with other financial institutions, we will share only your name, contact information, and information about your transactions.
